<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>文章 on 阿忠程式之路</title>
    <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 文章 on 阿忠程式之路</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-tw</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hitachi Content Platform 雲端平台</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/hcp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:05:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/hcp/</guid>
      <description>Hitachi Content Platform 此為Hitachi提供之檔案放置雲端平台之解決方案，參考API說明書，撰寫該元件之共用元件建立
提供以下服務
新增 刪除 更新 查詢 查詢範例 @Test void test_get_file_then_HcpGet_then_file() { HcpGet hcpDownloadInfo = new HcpGet(); String restPath = HcpUtil.toRestPath(&amp;#34;x.pdf&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;2&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;3&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;4&amp;#34;); hcpDownloadInfo.setPath(restPath); GetHcpInfo execute; try { execute = hcpService.execute(hcpDownloadInfo); String size = execute.getSize(); assertThat(size).isNotBlank(); } catch (HcpCodeExcepton e) { fail(&amp;#34;&amp;#34;); } } 刪除範例 @Test void test_delet_file_then_HcpGet_then_ok() { HcpDelete cmd = new HcpDelete(); String restPath = HcpUtil.toRestPath(&amp;#34;x.pdf&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;1&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;2&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;3&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;4&amp;#34;); cmd.setPath(restPath); try { BaseHcpInfo execute = hcpService.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>代碼元件</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/common-prop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 20:05:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/common-prop/</guid>
      <description>通用型代碼元件 解決問題：處理多來源之代碼元件統一方式處理， 並提供並提供代碼使用範圍，使用範圍定義為如下
資料範圍(CacheLoader&amp;lt;String, List &amp;lt;IProperties&amp;gt;&amp;gt;) 來源定義範圍內(例如：原有 A‘B與C 僅能修改此範圍內，且無法刪除，刪除則恢復預設值) 使用範圍:程式上使用參數，不得刪除
可擴充類型(例如：原有 A‘B與C還能增加額外項目) 使用範圍:類似帳號資料，管理者資料無法刪除，且可以增加額外項目
無基礎值(例如：原有 A‘B與C還能增加額外項目，且能全部刪除) 使用範圍: 資料可以任意清除
快取方式(IPropertieServiceHolder) 定時清除 使用範圍:資料有可能更新,特定時間清除
永久使用快取 使用範圍:資料永久不改變，沒有清除需要
不使用快取 使用範圍:資料強調正確性，可不使用快取
詳細說明參考 https://github.com/h8000572003/coomon-prooptics</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter VI: Esmeralda</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 11:25:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>We are delighted to be able to inform the reader, that during the whole of this scene, Gringoire and his piece had stood firm. His actors, spurred on by him, had not ceased to spout his comedy, and he had not ceased to listen to it. He had made up his mind about the tumult, and was determined to proceed to the end, not giving up the hope of a return of attention on the part of the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter V: Quasimodo</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2017 11:15:58 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>In the twinkling of an eye, all was ready to execute Coppenole’s idea. Bourgeois, scholars and law clerks all set to work. The little chapel situated opposite the marble table was selected for the scene of the grinning match. A pane broken in the pretty rose window above the door, left free a circle of stone through which it was agreed that the competitors should thrust their heads. In order to reach it, it was only necessary to mount upon a couple of hogsheads, which had been produced from I know not where, and perched one upon the other, after a fashion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter IV: Master Jacques Coppenole</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 11:14:48 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>While the pensioner of Ghent and his eminence were exchanging very low bows and a few words in voices still lower, a man of lofty stature, with a large face and broad shoulders, presented himself, in order to enter abreast with Guillaume Rym; one would have pronounced him a bull-dog by the side of a fox. His felt doublet and leather jerkin made a spot on the velvet and silk which surrounded him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter III: Monsieur the Cardinal</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Apr 2017 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>Poor Gringoire! the din of all the great double petards of the Saint-Jean, the discharge of twenty arquebuses on supports, the detonation of that famous serpentine of the Tower of Billy, which, during the siege of Paris, on Sunday, the twenty-sixth of September, 1465, killed seven Burgundians at one blow, the explosion of all the powder stored at the gate of the Temple, would have rent his ears less rudely at that solemn and dramatic moment, than these few words, which fell from the lips of the usher, “His eminence, Monseigneur the Cardinal de Bourbon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter II: Pierre Gringoire</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Apr 2017 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>Nevertheless, as be harangued them, the satisfaction and admiration unanimously excited by his costume were dissipated by his words; and when he reached that untoward conclusion: “As soon as his illustrious eminence, the cardinal, arrives, we will begin,” his voice was drowned in a thunder of hooting.
“Begin instantly! The mystery! the mystery immediately!” shrieked the people. And above all the voices, that of Johannes de Molendino was audible, piercing the uproar like the fife’s derisive serenade: “Commence instantly!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter I: The Grand Hall</title>
      <link>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gohugo-theme-ananke.pages.dev/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Three hundred and forty-eight years, six months, and nineteen days ago to-day, the Parisians awoke to the sound of all the bells in the triple circuit of the city, the university, and the town ringing a full peal.
The sixth of January, 1482, is not, however, a day of which history has preserved the memory. There was nothing notable in the event which thus set the bells and the bourgeois of Paris in a ferment from early morning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
